koenigcorp.com 2013-08-08

# Koenig Corporation Privacy Statement

**This website is administered by Koenig Corporation.**

**Your privacy on Koenig Corporation’s Website**

The primary purpose of Koenig Corporation’s website is to be a dynamic resource and business tool to help you create your future. We want you to feel secure when visiting our site and are committed to maintaining your privacy when doing so. The following provides an overview of how we protect your privacy during your visit.

**What information do we gather?**

Information on Koenig Corporation’s website is gathered in two ways: (1) indirectly (for example, through our site's technology); and (2) directly (for example, when you provide information on various pages of KoenigCorp.com).

One example of information we collect indirectly is through our Internet access logs. When you access Koenig Corporation’s website, your Internet address is automatically collected and is placed in our Internet access logs.

We collect information directly from you in a number of ways, some of which we describe in this Privacy Statement. One way is through the use of cookies. Cookies are small files of information which save and retrieve information about your visit to KoenigCorp.com—for example, how you entered our site, how you navigated through the site, and what information was of interest to you. The cookies we use identify you merely as a number. (If you are uncomfortable regarding cookies use, please keep in mind you can disable cookies on your computer by changing the settings in preferences or options menu in your browser.)

We also collect information when you voluntarily submit it to us. Throughout our site, we provide the opportunity to register for an event or conference, order a white paper, or participate in an online survey. When we collect this type of information, we will notify you as to why we are asking for information and how this information will be used. It is completely up to you whether or not you want to provide it.

**How do we use this information?**

We analyze it to determine what is most effective about our site, to help us identify ways to improve it, and eventually, to determine how we can tailor Koenig Corporation’s website to make it more effective. We may also use data for other purposes, which we would describe to you at the point we collect the information.

**Will we share this with outside parties?**

As a global organization, data we collect may be transferred internationally throughout Koenig Corporation's worldwide organization. We will not sell individual information and will share it only with our advisors. There will be other times when we need to share information, for example, in the case of an event where we need to provide our caterer with meal preference information. But again, before you submit any information, we will notify you as to why we are asking for specific information and it is completely up to you whether or not you want to provide it.

**What about sensitive personal data?**

We do not generally seek to collect sensitive personal data through this site. If we do seek to collect such data, we will ask you to consent to our proposed uses of the data. We may also collect some sensitive personal data incidentally. By providing us with unsolicited sensitive personal data, you consent to our using the data subject to applicable law as described in this Privacy Statement. The references to "sensitive personal data" are to the various categories of personal data identified by European and other data privacy laws as requiring special treatment, including in some circumstances the need to obtain explicit consent. These categories comprise personal identity numbers, personal data about personality and private life, racial or ethnic origin, nationality, political opinions, membership of political parties or movements, religious, philosophical or other similar beliefs, membership of a trade union or profession or trade association, physical or mental health, genetic code, addictions, sexual life, property matters or criminal record (including information about suspected criminal activities).

**Do we give you access to your information?**

You are entitled to know whether we hold information about you and, if we do, to have access to that information and require it to be corrected if it is inaccurate. You can do this by sending us an e-mail.

**What about data security?**

We take appropriate steps to maintain the security of your data on Koenig Corporation’s website. You should understand that the open nature of the Internet is such that data may flow over networks without security measures and may be accessed and used by people other than those for whom the data is intended.

That's it in a nutshell. The short of it is—we are interested in maintaining your privacy and creating a valuable resource for you to use. If you have any questions now or during your visit, please contact us.

Featured

What's Online Today!

Private Investors: 1,518

Partner Opportunities: 632,573

Venture Capital Companies: 2,118

Companies Seeking Capital: 23,388

Jobs & Projects 13,748

Thursday, August 08, 2013
